Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1887-1962; Series I; 16.18; 35 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Taylor, Loren, 1937–1941 (Box 27, Folder 1141)
    - Taylor, Pamela; Taylor, Francis Henry, 1941-1958, undated (Box 27, Folder 1142)
    - Taylor, Prentiss, 1943 March 13 (Box 27, Folder 1143)
    - Taylor, Ross McLaury; Taylor, Elizabeth Brooks, 1938–1943 (Box 27, Folder 1144)
    - Tcherepnin, Alexander, undated (Box 27, Folder 1145)
    - Ted Bates Advertising, 1951 November 19 (Box 27, Folder 1146)
    - Telegrams regarding "That Awful Mrs. Eaton", 1924 (Box 27, Folder 1147)
    - This Is War!, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 1148)
    - Thomas, A. E. (Albert Ellsworth), [?] August 4 (Box 27, Folder 1149)
    - Thomas, Charles M[arion?], 1943 May 16 (Box 27, Folder 1150)
    - Thomas, Elizabeth, undated (Box 27, Folder 1151)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1152)
    - Thompson, James Alden, 1935 November 5 (Box 27, Folder 1153)
    - Thompson, Randall, 1929, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 1154)
    - Thurber, James, 1944 May 19 (Box 27, Folder 1155)
    - Thursday Evening Club, 1937-1938, undated (Box 27, Folder 1156)
    - Time, 1923–1945 (Box 27, Folder 1157)
    - Timothy Dwight College (Yale University), 1941 November 14 (Box 27, Folder 1158)
    - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1938-1943, undated (Box 27, Folder 1159)
    - Todrin, Boris, 1936, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 1160)
    - Tombes, Andrew, 1942 July 26 (Box 27, Folder 1161)
    - Torrence, Ridgely, 1947 October 20 (Box 27, Folder 1162)
    - Tourtellot, Arthur Bernan, 1940–1943 (Box 27, Folder 1163)
    - Towle, Carroll S., 1939 March 28 (Box 27, Folder 1164)
    - Town & Country, 1927-1933, undated (Box 27, Folder 1165)
    - Town Hall, Inc., 1944–1947 (Box 27, Folder 1166)
    - Townsend, Marie, 1939 May 1 (Box 27, Folder 1167)
    - Train, Arthur, 1938-1945, undated (Box 27, Folder 1168)
    - Transition, 1936 October 31 (Box 27, Folder 1169)
    - Travers, P.L. (Pamela Lyndon), [?] December 23 (Box 27, Folder 1170)
    - Troubridge, Una Vincenzo, Lady, 1930, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 1171)
    - Tufts University, 1929 May 11 (Box 27, Folder 1172)
    - Turnbull, Agnes Sligh, 1941 January 26 (Box 27, Folder 1173)
    - Turner, Nancy Byrd, 1939 March 17 (Box 27, Folder 1174)
    - Tuttle, H. E. (Henry Emerson), 1938-1943, undated (Box 27, Folder 1175)
    - Twyefort, Frances, 1938–1951 (Box 27, Folder 1176)
    - "U" general, 1938-1949, undated (Box 28, Folder 1177)
    - Underwood, Arthur W., 1918 (Box 28, Folder 1178)
    - Underwood, [Lishe?], 1960-1961, undated (Box 28, Folder 1179)
    - Unesco, 1949 May 11 (Box 28, Folder 1180)
    - Union Trust Company of Pittsburgh, 1941 August 19 (Box 28, Folder 1181)
    - United Artists (Firm), 1929–1930 (Box 28, Folder 1182)
    - United Daughters of The Confederacy. Alabama Division, 1938, undated (Box 28, Folder 1183)
    - United Service Organizations (U.S.), 1941 July 24 (Box 28, Folder 1184)
    - United States. Army. Eastern Defense Command and First Army, 1942 April 28 (Box 28, Folder 1185)
    - United States. Defense Savings Staff, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 1186)
    - United States. Department of Agriculture, 1940–1943 (Box 28, Folder 1187)
    - United States. Department of the Army, 1948 August 3 (Box 28, Folder 1188)
    - Unites States. Department of State. Division of Libraries and Institutions, 1951 May 14 (Box 28, Folder 1189)
    - United States. Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1940, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 1190)
    - United States. Film Service, 1940 June 14 (Box 28, Folder 1191)
    - United States Military Academy, 1934–1941 (Box 28, Folder 1192)
    - United States. Office of Education, 1940 June 28 (Box 28, Folder 1193)
    - United States. Office of War Information, 1942–1944 (Box 28, Folder 1194)
    - United States. Treasury Department, 1941–1943 (Box 28, Folder 1195)
    - United States. War Department, 1940–1942 (Box 28, Folder 1196)
    - United States. Works Progress Administration, 1942 February 4 (Box 28, Folder 1197)
    - University of California, Berkeley. Library, 1955, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 1198)
    - University of Chicago, 1918–1942 (Box 28, Folder 1199)
    - University of Florida. Libraries, 1952 January 7 (Box 28, Folder 1200)
    - University of Georgia Press, 1941 November 21 (Box 28, Folder 1201)
    - University of Michigan, 1931, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 1202)
    - University of Mississippi. Library, 1962 February 7 (Box 28, Folder 1203)
    - University of Rochester, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 1204)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1939 June 2 (Box 28, Folder 1205)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1925–1947 (Box 28, Folder 1206)
    - "V" general, 1929-1962, undated (Box 28, Folder 1207)
    - Valentine, Alan Chester, 1954 May 3 (Box 28, Folder 1208)
    - Van Doren, Carl, 1922, 1937 (Box 28, Folder 1209)
    - Van Doren, Mark, 1943–1944 (Box 28, Folder 1210)
    - Van Hoosen, Bertha, 1927-1949, undated (Box 28, Folder 1211)
    - Van Loon, Hendrick Willem, 1943 March 13 (Box 28, Folder 1212)
    - Vanderlip, Narcissa cox, 1923, undated (Box 28, Folder 1213)
    - Vatsek, Joan, 1939–1943 (Box 28, Folder 1214)
    - Veeder, Grace Neahr, 1940, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 1215)
    - La Victoire, 1944 June 28 (Box 28, Folder 1216)
    - Viereck, Peter, 1939–1940 (Box 28, Folder 1217)
    - Viking Press, 1937, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 1218)
    - Vogue, 1921–1948 (Box 28, Folder 1219)
    - "W" general, 1916-1954, undated (Box 28, Folder 1220-1222)
    - W. W. Norton & Company, 1933–1956 (Box 28, Folder 1223)
    - Wagner, Charles A[braham], 1935 May 1 (Box 28, Folder 1224)
    - Walbridge, Earle Francis, 1958–1959 (Box 28, Folder 1225)
    - Walker, Charles R. (Charles Rumford), 1943 March 13 (Box 28, Folder 1226)
    - Walker, Margaret, 1940–1943 (Box 28, Folder 1227)
    - Wall, Bernhardt, 1938–1943 (Box 28, Folder 1228)
    - Wallace, Elizabeth, 1928-1958, undated (Box 29, Folder 1229-1231)
    - Wallace, Wesley H., 1937, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 1232)
    - Walser, Richard, 1950 October 19 (Box 29, Folder 1233)
    - Walsh, Chad, 1938 August 14 (Box 29, Folder 1234)
    - Walt Whitman Foundation, 1929 March 18 (Box 29, Folder 1235)
    - Walt Whitman Society of America, 1939-1943, undated (Box 29, Folder 1236)
    - Walter, Frank Keller, 1934 January 20 (Box 29, Folder 1237)
    - Ward, Julia, undated (Box 29, Folder 1238)
    - Warde, Beatrice, undated (Box 29, Folder 1239)
    - Warner Bros. Pictures (1923-1967), 1935 May 27 (Box 29, Folder 1240)
    - Warren, Lella, [?] March 12 (Box 29, Folder 1241)
    - Warren, Maude Rudford, [?] March 1 (Box 29, Folder 1242)
    - Washburn, Ruth W[endell?], 1959 June 4 (Box 29, Folder 1243)
    - Watermargin (Cornell University), 1949 February 5 (Box 29, Folder 1244)
    - Watkins, Ann, 1926–1927 (Box 29, Folder 1245)
    - Webster, Doris, 1940, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 1246)
    - Weill, Kurt, 1937 September 5 (Box 29, Folder 1247)
    - Weismiller, Edward, 1936-1943, undated (Box 29, Folder 1248)
    - Welles, Winifred, 1924 May 2 (Box 29, Folder 1249)
    - Wells, Carlton F. (Carlton Frank), 1933–1942 (Box 29, Folder 1250)
    - Wells College, 1939 June 2 (Box 29, Folder 1251)
    - Wenstrom, William H., 1941 July 5 (Box 29, Folder 1252)
    - Wescott, Glenway, 1943 March 15 (Box 29, Folder 1253)
    - Weygandt, Cornelius, 1942 October 16 (Box 29, Folder 1254)
    - Wheat, Clayton Earle; Wheat, Roberta, 1936-1943, undated (Box 29, Folder 1255)
    - Whigham, H. [J.?], 1929 [?] 30 (Box 29, Folder 1256)
    - White, Elise Fellows, 1940 May 17 (Box 29, Folder 1257)
    - White, Sarah [Harrison?], 1937 July 29 (Box 29, Folder 1258)
    - Whitehand, Robert, 1938, undated (Box 29, Folder 1259)
    - Whiteley, Mary N. S., 1943 April 16 (Box 29, Folder 1260)
    - Whitney, Janet, 1936–1960 (Box 29, Folder 1261)
    - Whitridge, Arnold; Whitridge, Janetta, 1933–1956 (Box 29, Folder 1262)
    - Whittlesey House, 1940 April 2 (Box 29, Folder 1263)
    - Widdemer, Margaret, 1933-1943, undated (Box 29, Folder 1264)
    - Wilde, Percival, 1937-1943, undated (Box 29, Folder 1265)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1930-1947, undated (Box 29, Folder 1266)
    - Wiley, Paul L. (Paul Luzon), 1944 April 30 (Box 29, Folder 1267)
    - William Morrow and Company, 1936 December 15 (Box 29, Folder 1268)
    - William Sloane Associates, Inc., 1949 (Box 29, Folder 1269)
    - Williams, Blanche Colton, 1932 July 2 (Box 29, Folder 1270)
    - Williams, Herschel, 1960–1961 (Box 29, Folder 1271)
    - Williams, Nathan B. (Nathan Boone), 1943 March 11 (Box 29, Folder 1272)
    - Williams, Oscar, 1941 October (Box 29, Folder 1273)
    - [Williams?], Valentine, 1936 January 22 (Box 29, Folder 1274)
    - Wilson, Hazel Hutchins, 1939 October 3 (Box 29, Folder 1275)
    - Wilson College (Chambersburg, Pa.), 1938 (Box 29, Folder 1276)
    - Winnipeg Free Press, 1940 September 6 (Box 29, Folder 1277)
    - Winter, Ruth; Winter, Pat, 1932, undated (Box 29, Folder 1278)
    - Wisconsin Historical Society, 1931 August 4 (Box 29, Folder 1279)
    - Wisdom, 1955 November 18 (Box 29, Folder 1280)
    - Wister, Owen, 1931-1936, undated (Box 29, Folder 1281)
    - WMCA, 1946, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 1282)
    - WNYE (Television Station: Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.), 1960 October 24 (Box 29, Folder 1283)
    - Woman's Day, 1942–1949 (Box 29, Folder 1284)
    - Wood, Clement, 1939 March 31 (Box 29, Folder 1285)
    - Wood, Lindsay L., 1929 June 27 (Box 29, Folder 1286)
    - Woodward, Elizabeth, 1940 August (Box 29, Folder 1287)
    - Woollcott, Alexander, 1942 November 5 (Box 30, Folder 1288)
    - Woollen, Evans, 1942 October 19 (Box 30, Folder 1289)
    - Woolley, Monty, 1941, undated (Box 30, Folder 1290)
    - Worcester Art Museum, 1933 December 1 (Box 30, Folder 1291)
    - Wright, Austin, 1941 August 26 (Box 30, Folder 1292)
    - [Wright, Richardson Little?], 1958, undated (Box 30, Folder 1293)
    - The Writer, 1940 April 25 (Box 30, Folder 1294)
    - Writer's War Board, 1942–1943 (Box 30, Folder 1295)
    - Wylie, Max, 1939 December 11 (Box 30, Folder 1296)
    - "Y" general, 1920-1943, undated (Box 30, Folder 1297)
    - Yaddo (Artists' Colony), 1937–1940 (Box 30, Folder 1298)
    - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1942-1943, undated (Box 30, Folder 1299)
    - Yale Club of New York City, 1960 March 16 (Box 30, Folder 1300)
    - The Yale Lit, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 1301)
    - The Yale Record, 1937, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 1302)
    - The Yale Review, 1930–1940 (Box 30, Folder 1303)
    - Yale School of Drama, 1959–1960 (Box 30, Folder 1304)
    - Yale University, 1918, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 1305)
    - Yale University Christian Association, 1939 November 17 (Box 30, Folder 1306)
    - Yale University Department of Personnel Study, 1935 December 16 (Box 30, Folder 1307)
    - Yale University Dramatic Association, 1927 May 20 (Box 30, Folder 1308)
    - Yale University. Library, 1916-1962, undated (Box 30, Folder 1309-1310)
    - Yale University. News Bureau, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 1311)
    - Yale University. Office of the Alumni Fund, 1944–1959 (Box 30, Folder 1312)
    - Yale University. Office of the Secretary, 1933–1948 (Box 30, Folder 1313)
    - Yale University. President's Office, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 1314)
    - Yale University Press, 1918-1958, undated (Box 30, Folder 1315-1316)
    - Yale University. Treasurer, 1938, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 1317)
    - Young, Collier, 1939, undated (Box 30, Folder 1318)
    - Young Men's Hebrew Association (New York, N.Y.), 1940 February 22 (Box 30, Folder 1319)
    - "Z" general, 1938 March 25 (Box 30, Folder 1320)
    - Zabriskie, George, 1940 June 4 (Box 30, Folder 1321)
    - Zimbalist, Efrem, 1929, undated (Box 30, Folder 1322)
    - Zoppola, Mara di, undated (Box 30, Folder 1323)
    - Condolence letters (A-C), 1943 March (Box 30, Folder 1324-1328)
    - Condolence letters (C-S), 1943 March (Box 31, Folder 1329-1343)
    - Condolence letters (S-W), 1943 March (Box 32, Folder 1344-1350)
    - Condolence letters (first name only), 1943 March (Box 32, Folder 1351)
    - "Strange Letters" (A-M), 1922-1961, undated (Box 32, Folder 1352-1358)
    - Printed illustration removed from "Strange Letters" (G), undated (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3115)
    - "Strange Letters" (O-W), 1922-1961, undated (Box 33, Folder 1359-1365)
    - First Name Only
      - "A" - "D", 1928-1947, undated (Box 33, Folder 1366)
      - "Allan", 1952 (Box 33, Folder 1367)
      - "Christine", 193[7?]-1941, undated (Box 33, Folder 1368)
      - "Cosette", 1923–1935 (Box 33, Folder 1369)
      - "Deborah", 1928, undated (Box 33, Folder 1370)
      - "E" - "F", 1921-1943, undated (Box 33, Folder 1371)
      - "Editha", 1933, undated (Box 33, Folder 1372)
      - "Elizabeth", undated (Box 33, Folder 1373)
      - "Epsie", 1953, undated (Box 33, Folder 1374)
      - "Fanny", undated (Box 33, Folder 1375)
      - "G" - "H", 1921-1944, udated (Box 33, Folder 1376)
      - "Helen", 1929–1930 (Box 33, Folder 1377)
      - "Henry", 1920-1922, undated (Box 33, Folder 1378)
      - "I" - "L", 1918-1962, undated (Box 33, Folder 1379)
      - "Lavinia", undated (Box 33, Folder 1380)
      - "Louisa", 1939-1942, undated (Box 33, Folder 1381)
      - "Louise", 1933, undated (Box 33, Folder 1382)
      - "M", 1921-1951, undated (Box 33, Folder 1383)
      - "Marian", undated (Box 34, Folder 1384)
      - "Muriel", 1947, undated (Box 34, Folder 1385)
      - "N" - "W", 1916-1959, undated (Box 34, Folder 1386)
      - "Phoebe", 1933, undated (Box 34, Folder 1387)
      - "Ruth", 1911-1913, undated (Box 34, Folder 1388)
    - Unidentified, 1912-1960, undated (Box 34, Folder 1389-1391)
    - Empty envelopes, 1953-1962, undated (Box 34, Folder 1392)
  - Third Party Correspondence
    - A. W. Head, Inc. to John Farrar, 1936 March 14 (Box 34, Folder 1393)
    - American University Union in Europe "To whom it may concern", 1919 April 26 (Box 34, Folder 1394)
    - Anderson, Lee to Farrar Rinehart, undated (Box 34, Folder 1395)
    - Baldwin, Henry to Charles A. Fenton, undated (Box 34, Folder 1396)
    - Baldwin, Sherman to Henry R. Hallowell, 1943 April 21 (Box 34, Folder 1397)
    - Book Publishers Bureau to New York Herald Tribune, 1943 March 16 (Box 34, Folder 1398)
    - Bowman, Earl to Wesley Winan Stout, 1939 July 11 (Box 34, Folder 1399)
    - Brand, Rachel to Mr. Zeigler, undated (Box 34, Folder 1400)
    - Brown, John, Jr. to Mrs. S. H. Brann, 1887 November 11 (Box 34, Folder 1401)
    - Chicago Tribune to unidentified, 1921 January 29 (Box 34, Folder 1402)
    - Cook, Mary S. to "Julia", undated (Box 34, Folder 1403)
    - Cruikshank, R. J. (Robert James) to British Press Service, 1941 November 6 (Box 34, Folder 1404)
    - Duffy, Frank P., Jr. to Philip S. Rose, 1938 April 29 (Box 34, Folder 1405)
    - Flanagan, John T. to Farrar Rinehart, 1941 June 20 (Box 34, Folder 1406)
    - G. P. Putnam's Sons to Stuart W. Jackson, 1945 March 24 (Box 34, Folder 1407)
    - Gillet, Edmond, Mrs. to Elizabeth Wallace, 1941 March 28 (Box 34, Folder 1408)
    - Green, Roy M. to Charles A. Fenton, undated (Box 34, Folder 1409)
    - Hart, Marguerite to Miss Gilman, undated (Box 34, Folder 1410)
    - Hills, John to "Morison", 1942 May 6 (Box 34, Folder 1411)
    - Hinckley to "Ella", 1929 January (Box 34, Folder 1412)
    - James, Philip to Dr. Damrosch, 1942 November 20 (Box 34, Folder 1413)
    - Jessup, Stephen W. to Doubleday, Doran and Company, 1928 August 21 (Box 34, Folder 1414)
    - Kennedy, Foster to [Susanna Valentine Mitchell?], [?] January 7 (Box 34, Folder 1415)
    - Lee, Eleanor Gay to Ella May Thornton, 1946 April 22 (Box 34, Folder 1416)
    - Leigh, W. Colston to Mrs. Hill, 1941 November 4 (Box 34, Folder 1417)
    - Lewis, Rachel to Amy Loveman, 1955 September 21 (Box 34, Folder 1418)
    - Linabury, Darcie to Dr. Lowrey, undated (Box 34, Folder 1419)
    - Lovett, Caroline Lewis to Mrs. Howard Meriwether Lovett, undated (Box 34, Folder 1420)
    - McBride, P. A., Mrs. To E. S. Morgan, 1942 March 17 (Box 34, Folder 1421)
    - Macmillan Company to Charles A. Fenton, 1956 November 27 (Box 34, Folder 1422)
    - Masters, Edgar Lee to John Farrar, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 1423)
    - [Miller?], Sarah to Book-of-the-Month Club, 1956 May 13 (Box 34, Folder 1424)
    - Moore, Douglas to E. C. Schirmer Music Company, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 1425)
    - Morgan, Aubrey to British Information Services, 1941 October 14 (Box 34, Folder 1426)
    - Morison, Stanley to Mrs. M. L. Becker, 1942 May 8 (Box 34, Folder 1427)
    - Motion Picture Producers and Distributors of America to Richard A. Rowland, 1940 September 17 (Box 34, Folder 1428)
    - Mount Vernon (Westchester, N.Y.). Dept. of Public Instruction to Brandt & Brandt, 1945 May 25 (Box 34, Folder 1429)
    - Musick, Eph. L. "To the Editor", 1943 January 17 (Box 34, Folder 1430)
    - National Broadcasting Company to Yale University Library, 1941 July 10 (Box 34, Folder 1431)
    - New York Public Library to Helen Adams, 1953 November 2 (Box 34, Folder 1432)
    - Page, Elizabeth to "Stan", 1942 October 12 (Box 34, Folder 1433)
    - Patterson, Mildred to Curtis Publishing Company, 1940 April 1 (Box 34, Folder 1434)
    - Pound, Ezra to National Institute of Arts and Letters (U.S.), 1940 March 20 (Box 34, Folder 1435)
    - Reichart, Rufus to American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1940 June 24 (Box 34, Folder 1436)
    - Reinfeld, George to Charles A. Fenton, undated (Box 34, Folder 1437)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington to [John] Farrar, 1928 June 4 (Box 34, Folder 1438)
    - Rollins, Carl Purlington to "Gilbert", undated (Box 34, Folder 1439)
    - Samuel Lippincott Borton to Wister, Owen, 1934 July 16 (Box 34, Folder 1440)
    - Sanborn, F. B. to John W. Dana, 1931 February 27 (Box 34, Folder 1441)
    - [Sevey?], Mary Jane to Rev. Moris Sante Campieri, 1921 November 27 (Box 34, Folder 1442)
    - Sharp, H. to Mr. Randall, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 1443)
    - Smith, Helen Jeannette to Charles A. Fenton, 1957 April 12 (Box 34, Folder 1444)
    - Stanley, Bennett to Book-of-the-Month Club, 1953 September 26 (Box 34, Folder 1445)
    - Stevens, S. K. to J. Bennet Nolan, 1941 October 15 (Box 34, Folder 1446)
    - Strong, Phil to "John", 1939 July 20 (Box 34, Folder 1447)
    - Stuart, Agnes E. to Berthe des Combes Favard, 1929 January 5 (Box 34, Folder 1448)
    - Sudler, Culbreth to Charles A. Fenton, 1954, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 1449)
    - Swanson, Neil to "John and Stan", 1940 June 11 (Box 34, Folder 1450)
    - Tower, Fred A. to John W. Dana, 1931 February 19 (Box 34, Folder 1451)
    - Untermeyer, Louis to Mr. Rinehart, 1925 September 3 (Box 34, Folder 1452)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1920 October 5 (Box 34, Folder 1453)
    - Wallace, Elizabeth to Richard Myers and Alice Lee Myers, 1945, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 1454)
    - Yale University Press to Donald Gallup, 1960 October 10 (Box 34, Folder 1455)
    - [?]egley, Dorothy to Brandt & Brandt, [?] October 17 (Box 34, Folder 1456)
    - "Carol" to John Poster, 1941 November 10 (Box 34, Folder 1457)
    - Unidentified to Elizabeth Page, 1942 October 15 (Box 34, Folder 1458)
- Family Correspondence, 1829-1962; Series II; 6.05; 15 boxes
  Organized into two subseries: General Correspondence and Other Family Letters. General Correspondence is arranged alphabetically first by correspondent (sender), then by recipient. The first correspondent (sender), for example, is Barton, Alexander, followed by Baxter, Lora. Letters are arranged chonologically within files.
  Series II. Family Correspondence consists chiefly of letters between members of the Benét, Carr, and Rose families. There are large files of original correspondence from Stephen Vincent to his mother, Frances Rose Benét, and to his wife Rosemary, and from Rosemary to Stephen Vincent. Letters to and from in-laws are also found here, including Kathleen and Charles Gilman Norris and Elinor Wylie. The Other Family Letters subseries includes third-party letters from non-family members.
  Letters to Stephen Vincent Benét from Andrew Jones, a cousin, are located in Series I. Correspondence, General Correspondence, Boxes 15-16, folders 624-638.
  - General Correspondence
    - Barton, Alexander
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1919-1920, undated (Box 35, Folder 1459-1461)
    - Baxter, Lora
      - Benét, Rosemary, undated (Box 35, Folder 1462)
    - "Benét family"
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1924-1940, undated (Box 35, Folder 1463)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1921-1939, undated (Box 35, Folder 1464)
    - Benét, Frances Rose (mother)
      - Benét children, 1933-1938, undated (Box 35, Folder 1465)
      - Benét, Laurence Vincent, 1926, undated (Box 35, Folder 1466)
      - Benét, Margaret Cox, undated (Box 35, Folder 1467)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1927-1939, undated (Box 35, Folder 1468-1474)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1910–1919 (Box 35, Folder 1475-1476)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1920–1936 (Box 36, Folder 1477-1489)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1936-1939, undated (Box 37, Folder 1490-1501)
      - Carr, Rachel H., 1926, undated (Box 37, Folder 1502)
      - Rose, William J., undated (Box 37, Folder 1503)
      - Others, 1928, undated (Box 37, Folder 1504)
    - Benét, James Walker (father)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, undated (Box 37, Folder 1505)
      - Benét, Laura, 1898 July 22 (Box 37, Folder 1506)
      - Benét, Laurence Vincent, 1891-1924, undated (Box 37, Folder 1507)
      - Benét, Margaret Cox, 1919, undated (Box 37, Folder 1508)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1903–1928 (Box 38, Folder 1509-1513)
      - Samson, ----, undated (Box 38, Folder 1514)
    - Benét, James, 1914- (nephew)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1933-1954, undated (Box 38, Folder 1515)
    - Benét, Kathleen Anne (niece)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1948, undated (Box 38, Folder 1516)
    - Benét, Laura (sister)
      - Benét, Laurence Vincent, 1895 Janaury 9 (Box 38, Folder 1517)
      - Benét, Margaret Cox, 1928 April 26 (Box 38, Folder 1518)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1922-1962, undated (Box 38, Folder 1519-1525)
      - Benét, Stephanie, undated (Box 38, Folder 1526)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1910-1942, undated (Box 39, Folder 1527-1533)
      - Clipping removed from Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1942 January 7 (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3116)
      - Benét, Thomas, 1944 June 3 (Box 39, Folder 1534)
      - Benét, William Rose, 1940 February 18 (Box 39, Folder 1535)
      - [Rose, M. L.], undated (Box 39, Folder 1536)
    - Benét, Laurence Vincent (uncle)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1931, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 1537)
      - Benét, James Walker, 1919 November 24 (Box 39, Folder 1538)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1934-1948, undated (Box 39, Folder 1539-1541)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1914-1942, undated (Box 39, Folder 1542-1544)
      - Others, 1934, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 1545)
    - Benét, Margaret Cox (aunt-in-law)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1931-1937, undated (Box 39, Folder 1546)
      - Benét, Laura, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 1547)
      - Benét, Rosemary, 1921-1941, undated (Box 40, Folder 1548-1552)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1922-1941, undated (Box 40, Folder 1553-1555)
    - Benét, Mildred A. (cousin)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1932 April 21 (Box 40, Folder 1556)
    - Benét, Rachel (daughter)
      - Benét, Rosemary, undated (Box 40, Folder 1557)
    - Benét, Rosemary
      - Benét children, undated (Box 40, Folder 1558)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, 1927–1939 (Box 40, Folder 1559)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1921-1939, undated (Box 40, Folder 1560-1564)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, undated (Box 41, Folder 1565-1574)
      - Carr, Rachel H., 1905–1922 (Box 41, Folder 1575)
    - Benét, S. V. (Stephen Vincent) (grandfather)
      - Johnson, Andrew, undated (Box 41, Folder 1576)
      - Walker, J. R., 1833 July 13 (Box 41, Folder 1577)
    - Benét, Stephanie (daughter)
      - Benét, Frances Rose, undated (Box 41, Folder 1578)